Scenic Hudson Collection: Records Relating to the Storm King Case, 1963-1981
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 12. Public Service Commission, 1968-1977; 12; About 1.5 linear feet Boxes: 106 - 110 Folders: 1510 - 1570
  Series contains reports, testimony, minutes of hearings, exhibits, briefs, policy statements, clippings, bulletins, and press releases documenting the role of the PSC in the Storm King case, 1967-1977. Papers are arranged chronologically.
  - Board of Public Utility Commissioners: Newark, NJ; Tuesday Jan. 3, 1967 (1510, Box 106)
  - Board of Public Utility Commissioners: Newark NJ; Wednesday Jan. 4, 1967 (Folder 1511, Box 106)
  - Public Service Commission: Report on Blackout; March 1967 (Folder 1512, Box 106)
  - Public Service Commission: Alexander Saunders Statement; August 8, 1969 (Folder 1513, Box 106)
  - Public Service Commission: Remarks by Comptroller, M.A. Procaccino; Aug. 25, 1969 (Folder 1514, Box 106)
  - Public Service Commission: Minutes of Hearing; Oct. 21, 1969 (Folder 1515, Box 106)
  - Public Service Commission: Cases 25741 and 25845 - Testimonies; Nov. 7, 1969 (Folder 1516, Box 106)
  - Scenic Hudson Preservation Conference: Public Service Commission - Schedule of Hearings; 1971 (Folder 1517, Box 106)
  - Public Service Commission - Testimony in Case 25352; Nov. 1971 (Folder 1518, Box 106)
  - Public Service Commission - Opinion and Order Establishing Rules and Regulations - Re: Underground Electric, Telephone,& Telegraph Facilities; Dec. 28, 1971 (Folder 1519, Box 106)
  - Public Service Commission - Recommended Decision by Examiner Boschwitz, Jan. 20, 1972 (Folder 1520, Box 106)
  - Public Service Commission - Testimonies and Related Material; Dec. 1972 - April 1973 (1521, Box 107)
  - Public Service Commission - Testimonies and Related Material; May 1973 (Folder 1522, Box 107)
  - Public Service Commission - Testimony before, c. May 1973 (Folder 1523, Box 107)
  - Public Testimonies Commission - Testimony and Related Material; June 1973 and Undated (Folder 1524, Box 107)
  - Public Service Commission - Testimony before, June - July 1973 (Folder 1525, Box 107)
  - Public Service Commission - Case # 25293 - Exhibits (Folder 1526, Box 107)
  - Public Service Commission - Butzel Letter re: Con Ed Ads; Aug. 28, 1973 (Folder 1527, Box 107)
  - Public Service Commission: New York City Brief - Case # 26292; Sept. 26, 1973 (Folder 1528, Box 107)
  - Public Service Commission - Policy Statements; 1973 (Folder 1529, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission - Report on Energy Conservation in Space Conditioning; Jan. 31, 1974 (Folder 1530, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Comment on Rochester Gas& Electric Corp. on Recommended Decision; 2/15/74 (Folder 1531, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Scenic Hudson, et al - Re: Block Decision; Feb. 15, 1974 (Folder 1532, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: CE Rates - New York City Brief on Exemptions; Feb. 16, 1974 (Folder 1533, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Scenic Hudson, et al -Re: Jones on Energy Conservation, Feb. 19, 1974 (Folder 1534, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Scenic Hudson Objection of Construction Contract; Feb 20, 1974 (Folder 1535, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: CE Rate Case - Order Denying Rehearing; April 29, 1974 (Folder 1536, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: CE Rate Case - Atty. General Louis Lefkowitz; June 11, 1974 (Folder 1537, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Memo of NYC Law in Support of Petition and in Opposition to Motion to Dismiss; July 22, 1974 (Folder 1538, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Judge Williams Decision; Oct. 1, 1974 (Folder 1539, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Long Range Electric Plans; Nov. 26, 1974 (Folder 1540, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Answer to Con Ed Deferral Request; March 18, 1975 (Folder 1541, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Scenic Hudson Reply to Con Ed Deferral Request; March 26, 1975 (Folder 1542, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Order Questioning Necessity and Feasibility; June 26, 1975 (Folder 1543, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Long Range Electric Plan, Aug. 7, 1965 (Folder 1544, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Petition of Empire State Power Resources, Inc. Sept. 30, 1975 (Folder 1545, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Rates, Rules and Regulations of Long Island Lighting Company; March - April 1976 (Folder 1546, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Order Granting Reconsideration and Modifying Deadlines; May 11, 1976 (Folder 1547, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Scenic Hudson Comments on Con Ed Cornwall Report, Recommendations; June 11, 1976 (Folder 1548, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Opinion and Order on Relevance of Marginal Costs to Electric Rate Structures; Aug. 10, 1976 (Folder 1549, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Lifeline Rate Issue; Dec. 7, 1976 (Folder 1550, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Order Extending Deadline for Pre-filing of Testimony and Exhibits; Feb. 3, 1977 (Folder 1551, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Steam Electric Generating Facilities; 1977 (Folder 1552, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Rate Design; 1975-78 (Folder 1553, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Comparative Economics of Nuclear/Fossil Fuel; 1976-77 (Folder 1554, Box 108)
  - Public Service Commission: Energy Consumption Analysis on Buildings in the New York Area (Folder 1555, Box 109)
  - Public Service Commission: Annual Report; Dec. 31, 1970 (Folder 1556, Box 109)
  - Public Service Commission: Reports; 1972-73 (Folder 1557, Box 109)
  - Public Service Commission: Complaint Reaction; 1973 (Folder 1558, Box 109)
  - Public Service Commission: Joseph C. Swidler; 1970-72 (Folder 1559, Box 109)
  - Public Service Commission: Con Edison Rates; 1970-72 (Folder 1560, Box 109)
  - Public Service Commission: Alternative Energy Systems Analysis of Lower Manhattan Landing Project (Folder 1561, Box 109)
  - Public Service Commission - Gas Plan; 1967 (1562, Box 110)
  - Public Service Commission: Con Ed Rate Case; 1970 (Folder 1563, Box 110)
  - NYS Public Service Commission - Wm K. Jones at Columbia Law Symposium; March 20, 1971 (Folder 1564, Box 110)
  - Public Service Commission: Power Plant Siting Law; 1971 (Folder 1565, Box 110)
  - Public Service Commission: Attack of PSC Examiners; 1971 (Folder 1566, Box 110)
  - Public Service Commission: Con Ed Service (Folder 1567, Box 110)
  - Public Service Commission: Clippings (Folder 1568, Box 110)
  - Public Service Commission: Weekly Bulletin; 7/18/72 (Folder 1569, Box 110)
  - Public Service Commission: Publicity Releases (Folder 1570, Box 110)
- 13. Sherwood, Helen, 1962-1974; 13; About 3 linear feet Boxes: 111 - 116 Folders: 1571 - 1644
  Series contains correspondence, press releases subject files, printed matter, and clippings on the Storm King case collected by Miss Sherwood, an active member of Scenic Hudson, Inc.
  Alphabetical and Chronological
  - Correspondence: A - M (Folder 1571, Box 111)
  - Correspondence: Hatch, Allene (Folder 1572, Box 111)
  - Correspondence: N - Z (Folder 1573, Box 111)
  - Federal Power Commission: General (Folder 1574, Box 111)
  - Federal Power Commission: Legal Papers (Folder 1575, Box 111)
  - Federal Power Commission: Testimony A - G (Folder 1576, Box 111)
  - FPC Testimony: H - W (Folder 1577, Box 112)
  - FPC Testimony: Mullarkey (Folder 1578, Box 112)
  - Intervenors (Folder 1579, Box 112)
  - Maps of Hudson Highlands (Folder 1580, Box 112)
  - Press Releases, etc. 1964-65 (Folder 1581, Box 112)
  - Press Releases, etc. 1966-71 (Folder 1582, Box 112)
  - Press Releases 1972 and Undated (Folder 1583, Box 112)
  - North American Wildlife and Natural Resources Conference (Folder 1584, Box 112)
  - (Box 112)
  - Ottinger, Richard (Folder 1585, Box 112)
  - Scenic Hudson Board of Directors Meetings - Agenda& Minutes (Folder 1586, Box 113)
  - 975 (1970, Box 113)
  - Scenic Hudson Board of Directors Meetings - Agenda& Minutes (Folder 1587, Box 113)
  - (Box 113)
  - Scenic Hudson Board of Directors Meetings - Agenda& Minutes (Folder 1588, Box 113)
  - (Box 113)
  - Scenic Hudson Board of Directors - Memos to (Folder 1589, Box 113)
  - Scenic Hudson, Inc.: Misc. (Folder 1590, Box 113)
  - Scenic Hudson, Inc.: Bulletins (Folder 1591, Box 113)
  - Scenic Hudson News (Folder 1592, Box 113)
  - Scenic Hudson Brief by Dale E. Doty; April 8, 1965 (Folder 1593, Box 113)
  - Sierra Club: FPC Brief& Testimony; 1967 (Folder 1594, Box 113)
  - Sierra Club Brief; Aug. 14, 1967 (Folder 1595, Box 113)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals Brief (Folder 1596, Box 113)
  - United States FPC - Presiding Examiners Initial Decision; 8/6/68 (Folder 1597, Box 114)
  - FPC - Applicant’s Brief; Aug. 14, 1967 (Folder 1598, Box 114)
  - Commission Staff Brief on Exceptions; Oct. 7, 1968 (Folder 1599, Box 114)
  - Commission Staff Brief Opposing Exceptions; Oct. 28, 1968 (Folder 1600, Box 114)
  - SHPC& The Atlantic Chapter of the Sierra Club; 9/22/69 (Folder 1601, Box 114)
  - FPC - Applicant’s Brief; Jan. 22, 1970 (Folder 1602, Box 114)
  - FPC - Brief of Applicant; April 25, 1969 (Folder 1603, Box 114)
  - FPC - Brief on Exceptions for Applicant; Oct. 7, 1968 (Folder 1604, Box 114)
  - FPC - Brief Opposing Exceptions for Applicant; Oct. 24, 1968 (Folder 1605, Box 114)
  - Opinion& Order Issuing License… - March 9, 1965 (Folder 1606, Box 114)
  - Reply Brief of Sierra Club (Folder 1607, Box 114)
  - Commission Staff Supplemental Brief; April 25, 1969 (Folder 1608, Box 114)
  - Brief on Behalf of SHPC, Intervenor (Folder 1609, Box 114)
  - Opinion& Order Issuing License… 8/19/70 (Folder 1610, Box 114)
  - Opinion& Order Issuing License… 3/9/65 (Folder 1611, Box 114)
  - Presiding Examiner’s Initial Decision… 8/6/68 (Folder 1612, Box 114)
  - Supreme Court of the United States; Oct. Term 1971 (Folder 1613, Box 115)
  - Federal Focal Point in Outdoor Recreation (Folder 1614, Box 115)
  - Federal Assistance in Outdoor Recreation (Folder 1615, Box 115)
  - Creation of a Natural Trust (Folder 1616, Box 115)
  - The Cornwall Project (Folder 1617, Box 115)
  - America the (Formerly) Beautiful (Folder 1618, Box 115)
  - National Forests, Parks, Monuments… (Folder 1619, Box 115)
  - Register Christian Opinion; 1965 (Folder 1620, Box 115)
  - Action for Outdoor Recreation for America (Folder 1621, Box 115)
  - America’s Dept. of Natural Resources (Folder 1622, Box 115)
  - Congressional Record (Folder 1623, Box 115)
  - Beware of the Pied Pipers… (Folder 1624, Box 115)
  - Open Space Action Committee (Program) (Folder 1625, Box 115)
  - Alden Research Laboratories; March 1969 (Folder 1626, Box 115)
  - Con Edison 1968 Annual Report (Folder 1627, Box 115)
  - Storm over Storm King (Folder 1628, Box 115)
  - The Hudson River for Whose Utility? (Folder 1629, Box 115)
  - Hudson River Fisheries Investigations; 1965-68 (Folder 1630, Box 115)
  - Saving the Wilderness (Field and Stream); Aug. 1973 (Folder 1631, Box 115)
  - Natural History; June-July 1965 (Folder 1632, Box 115)
  - Field and Stream; March 1965 (Folder 1633, Box 115)
  - 1969 Citizens Conservation Dinner (Folder 1634, Box 115)
  - Printed Matter (Folder 1635, Box 115)
  - Clean Water (Folder 1636, Box 115)
  - Clippings; 1962-64 (Folder 1637, Box 116)
  - Clippings; 1963-64 (Folder 1638, Box 116)
  - Clippings; 1965 (Folder 1639, Box 116)
  - Clippings; 1965 (Folder 1640, Box 116)
  - Clippings - Blackout; Nov. 9, 1965 (Folder 1641, Box 116)
  - Clippings - Cornwall (Folder 1642, Box 116)
  - Clippings (Copies); c.1966-74 (Folder 1643, Box 116)
  - Clippings; 1966-75 and Undated (Folder 1644, Box 116)
- 14. Studies, Reports, Statements, Notes, Drafts, and Background Materials, 1958-1977; 14; About 3 linear feet Boxes: 117 - 124 Folders: 1645 - 1736
  Series contains materials used in the preparation of legal documents and publicity materials, and the scholarly papers written about the case. A complete list of documents is available in the shelf list..
  - “An Alternative to Storm King” Nov. 30, 1973 (Folder 1645, Box 117)
  - “A Modified Alternative to Storm King” Komanoff/Semmel, May 22, 1974 (Folder 1646, Box 117)
  - “The Calvert Cliffs Decision” (Folder 1647, Box 117)
  - “The City and Electric Power” (Folder 1648, Box 117)
  - Cleary Study (Folder 1649, Box 117)
  - College of the Atlantic’s Storm King Reader (Folder 1650, Box 117)
  - “Con Ed: Proposed Astoria Expansion” (Folder 1651, Box 117)
  - “Cost and Fuel Savings Attributable to the Alternative to Storm King” (Folder 1652, Box 117)
  - “Deep Wells for Industrial Waste Injection in the United States” (Folder 1653, Box 118)
  - “The Defense of Fort Montgomery” (Folder 1654, Box 118)
  - “Environment and the Law” (Folder 1655, Box 118)
  - “Environmental Activism: The Fight Over Storm King - A Legal History” (Folder 1656, Box 118)
  - “Environmental Impacts of Indian Point Unit No. 2 Operation with Unit No. 1 Operation” (Folder 1657, Box 118)
  - “Ground Water Contamination” (Folder 1658, Box 118)
  - “A General Management Plan for Gateway National Recreation Area” (Folder 1659, Box 118)
  - Hudson River Ecology (Folder 1660, Box 118)
  - “The Hudson River - For Whose Utility?” (Folder 1661, Box 118)
  - Indian Point Generating Station Entrainment Survival and Related Studies, 1977 Annual Report (Folder 1662, Box 119)
  - “Influence of Indian Point Unit 2” Errata (Folder 1663, Box 119)
  - Institute of Environmental Medicine Hudson River Ecosystem Studies (Folder 1664, Box 119)
  - “Injustice and the Environment: A Moral Dilemma” (Folder 1665, Box 119)
  - 1975 Year-Class Report for the Multiplan Impact Study of the Hudson River Estuary (Folder 1666, Box 119)
  - New York Power Pool - Map (Folder 1667, Box 119)
  - New York State Supreme Court Decision re Water Quality, Mar. (Folder 1668, Box 119)
  - An Organizers Notebook on Public Utilities and Energy (Folder 1669, Box 119)
  - “The Politics of an Environmental Interest Group: A Case Study of the Scenic Hudson Preservation Conference” (Folder 1670, Box 120)
  - Questionnaires (Folder 1671, Box 120)
  - Recreation - Hudson Valley Association (Folder 1672, Box 120)
  - Regional Plan Association (Folder 1673, Box 120)
  - Research and Development (Folder 1674, Box 120)
  - Research Reports “Accidents Caused by Electric Power Lines” (Folder 1675, Box 120)
  - “Artistic and Historical Value of the Hudson” (Folder 1676, Box 120)
  - “Collapse of Texas Tower 4” (Folder 1677, Box 120)
  - “Conservation Victories”, “Cash Value of Conservation” “Conservation Law” (Folder 1678, Box 121)
  - “Consolidated Edison and the Rockefeller Family” (Folder 1679, Box 121)
  - Research Reports: Other (Folder 1680, Box 121)
  - “Parks - Palisades Interstate” (Folder 1681, Box 121)
  - “Requiem for a River” (Folder 1682, Box 121)
  - Gov. Rockefeller’s Newly Proposed Law re: Public Service (Folder 1683, Box 121)
  - Sporn, Philip - Writings on the Environment (Folder 1684, Box 121)
  - Statistics - Hudson Valley Project, 1958 - 1965 (Folder 1685, Box 121)
  - Statistics - Hudson Valley Project, 1966-71 (Folder 1686, Box 121)
  - Statistics - Hudson Valley Project, Misc. and Undated (Folder 1687, Box 121)
  - Statistics on Power Systems (Folder 1688, Box 121)
  - “Storm King: A Lethargy of Uncivilized Nature” (Folder 1689, Box 122)
  - Storm King Highway (Folder 1690, Box 122)
  - “The Storm Over Storm King” (Folder 1691, Box 122)
  - Sub-Committee on Fisheries and Wildlife Conservation and the Environment Hearings, Feb. 19 - 20, 1974 (Folder 1692, Box 122)
  - “Supervision of Dams by State Authorities” July 1966 (Folder 1693, Box 122)
  - Technology (Folder 1694, Box 122)
  - Temporary Committee to Study the Catskills, Interim Report, Mar. (Folder 1695, Box 122)
  - Texas Instruments Studies (Folder 1696, Box 122)
  - Thermal Pollution (Folder 1697, Box 122)
  - “Three Views on the Power Crisis” (Folder 1698, Box 122)
  - Tidal Power (Folder 1699, Box 122)
  - “Toward a Rational Power Policy” (Folder 1700, Box 122)
  - Union Electric Report to Missouri Public Service Commission re (Folder 1701, Box 122)
  - “Utilities and the Hudson River” (Folder 1702, Box 123)
  - “Water Quality in Industrial Areas” (Folder 1703, Box 123)
  - “Nuclear Power Plants Underground” (Folder 1704, Box 123)
  - “Study of Room Air Conditioners” (Folder 1705, Box 123)
  - “Seepage Problems of Pumped Storage” (Folder 1706, Box 123)
  - “Power and Responsibility” (Folder 1707, Box 123)
  - “Southern California Repowers with Combined Cycle” (Folder 1708, Box 123)
  - Statement on Storm King (Folder 1709, Box 123)
  - “Potential Effects of Hudson River Power Plants” (Folder 1710, Box 123)
  - “Consideration of Other Power Plants” (Folder 1711, Box 123)
  - “Assessment of the Impact of Storm King on the Striped Bass” (Folder 1712, Box 123)
  - “An Alternative to Storm King” - Counter Rebuttal (Folder 1713, Box 123)
  - “PASNY Takeover and Storm King” (Folder 1714, Box 123)
  - “Balancing the Uses of a Limited Resource” (Folder 1715, Box 123)
  - “Cost and Fuel Savings Attributable to the Alternative to Storm (Folder 1716, Box 123)
  - Consolidated Edison Publicity Release, Jul. 25, 1974 (Folder 1717, Box 123)
  - “Studies of the Hudson River Ecology” (Folder 1718, Box 123)
  - “Union Carbide and National Energy Problems -- Petrochemicals” (Folder 1719, Box 123)
  - “Congress Asked to Hold Hearings on FPC Bias” March 18, 1976 (Folder 1720, Box 123)
  - Draft of Motion to Terminate License, Sept. 13, 1976 (Folder 1721, Box 123)
  - Speech on Alternative Energy, Nov. 20, 1976 (Folder 1722, Box 123)
  - “Scenic Hudson Brands FPC ‘Insensitive’ to Public Issues” Dec. (Folder 1723, Box 123)
  - Blackout, Jul. 13, 1977 (Folder 1724, Box 123)
  - “Energy and American Civilization” (Folder 1725, Box 123)
  - Con Ed System - All Turbine Alternative (Folder 1726, Box 123)
  - Statement of William Vickrey (Folder 1727, Box 123)
  - “Storm King: The Great Environmental Debate” (Folder 1728, Box 123)
  - “The Politics of an Environmental Interest Group” (Incomplete) (Folder 1729, Box 123)
  - “The Therapeutic Significance of Bird Protection and Bird (Folder 1730, Box 123)
  - Background Material (Folder 1731, Box 124)
  - Background Material (Folder 1732, Box 124)
  - Notes and Drafts (Folder 1733, Box 124)
  - Notes and Drafts (Folder 1734, Box 124)
  - Reports (Folder 1735, Box 124)
  - Statements (Folder 1736, Box 124)
- 15. Series title, 1964-1974; 15; About 10 linear feet Boxes: 125 - 156 Folders: 1737 - 2067
  Series contains information on a variety of topics, arranged alphabetically. These files contain some of the earliest material collected by the group. Similar material is found under Other Organizations and Printed Matter. Subjects include Blackouts, Catskill Aqueduct, Central Hudson Gas and Electric Company, Cornwall Project, Dams, Edison Electric Institute, Environmental Concerns, Gas Turbines, Geological Data, Highways, Hudson River Expressway, Hudson River Valley Commission, Hudson Valley Project, Interior Department, Natural Area Council, Nuclear Power, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, Pollution, Power Lines, Power Plants, Pumped Storage, Radio and Television, Storm King, U.S. Court of Appeals, Utilities, Water, Wetlands, Wilderness Society, and Yorktown.
  - Alternatives (Folder 1737, Box 125)
  - Serge Korff, American Geographic Society (Folder 1738, Box 125)
  - Atomic and Nuclear Power (Folder 1739, Box 125)
  - Bequests (Folder 1740, Box 125)
  - Blackout, The Great NE; 11/9/65 (Folder 1741, Box 125)
  - Blackout, The Great NE; 11/9/65 - Printed Matter (Folder 1742, Box 125)
  - Saunders Statement, re: Blackout; 12/8/65 (Folder 1743, Box 125)
  - Blackouts - Scenic Hudson Stand (Folder 1744, Box 125)
  - Blackouts other than The Great NE Blackout of Nov. ‘65 (Folder 1745, Box 125)
  - Blackouts - Reports by Alexander Lurkis (Folder 1746, Box 126)
  - Lurkis - Blackout KIT for Press (Folder 1747, Box 126)
  - Blackout Prevention - Reprints (Folder 1748, Box 126)
  - Blackout Prevention - Clippings (Folder 1749, Box 126)
  - Larry Bogart - 1968-69 (Anti Pollution League) (Folder 1750, Box 126)
  - Breakneck Mountain; 1963 (Folder 1751, Box 126)
  - BRINCO (Folder 1752, Box 126)
  - Brooklyn Union Gas Company (Folder 1753, Box 126)
  - Brownouts; 1970 (Folder 1754, Box 126)
  - Brownouts; 1970 (Folder 1755, Box 126)
  - Burger, Warren - Decision; June 20, 1969 (Folder 1756, Box 126)
  - Businessmen for the Public Interest, 1971 (Folder 1757, Box 126)
  - California Scenic Conservation Laws - Hudson Valley Project (Folder 1758, Box 127)
  - Calvert Cliffs, MD - Court Decision; 1971 [AEC] (Folder 1759, Box 127)
  - Capacity (Generating), 1964-70 (Folder 1760, Box 127)
  - CAPCO (Central Area Power Coordination Group) (Hudson Valley Project) (Folder 1761, Box 127)
  - Cartoon (Citizen Smith) corres. (Folder 1762, Box 127)
  - Catskill Aqueduct (Folder 1763, Box 127)
  - Catskill Aqueduct (Folder 1764, Box 127)
  - Catskill Aqueduct (Folder 1765, Box 127)
  - Central Hudson Gas&Electric - Hudson Valley Project; 1962-68 (Folder 1766, Box 127)
  - Central Hudson Gas&Electric - Hudson Valley Project; 1967-69 (Folder 1767, Box 127)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Folder 1768, Box 128)
  - Citizens Information Committee, Cornwall NY (Hudson Valley (Folder 1769, Box 128)
  - Coal (Folder 1770, Box 128)
  - Commonwealth Edison - Chicago (Folder 1771, Box 128)
  - Condemnation - State Lands by Utility (Hudson Valley Project) (Folder 1772, Box 128)
  - Congressional Records (Folder 1773, Box 128)
  - Congressional Record (Folder 1774, Box 128)
  - Connecticut Legislative Bill 4546 - Hearings; March 8/1967 - (Folder 1775, Box 128)
  - Connecticut Valley Action Committee (Folder 1776, Box 128)
  - Conservation Department (NYS) (Hudson Valley Project) (Folder 1777, Box 128)
  - Conservation Seminars and Meetings; 1971 (Folder 1778, Box 128)
  - Constitution Island Association (Hudson Valley Project) (Folder 1779, Box 128)
  - Cooperating Organizations (Hudson Valley Project) (Folder 1780, Box 128)
  - Cornwall Project (Folder 1781, Box 128)
  - Cornwall: Immediate Follow - Up (Folder 1782, Box 128)
  - Dams (Folder 1783, Box 129)
  - Dam Failures - Correspondence and Memoranda (Folder 1784, Box 129)
  - Dam Failures - Clippings (Folder 1785, Box 129)
  - Dam Failures - Reference Material (Folder 1786, Box 129)
  - Dam Failures - Reports and Printed Matter (Folder 1787, Box 129)
  - Re: Dredging on L.I. - R.V. (Folder 1788, Box 129)
  - Earth Dam Story (Folder 1789, Box 129)
  - Earthquakes (Folder 1790, Box 129)
  - Edison Electric Institute (Folder 1791, Box 130)
  - Edison Electric Institute Reports, 1965-68, 1970-71 (Folder 1792, Box 130)
  - Electric Cars (Folder 1793, Box 130)
  - Electric Power for the Future; Aug. 1971 - Dept. of Engineering, Swarthmore College (Folder 1794, Box 130)
  - Electricity (Folder 1795, Box 130)
  - Endangered Fish&Wildlife (Folder 1796, Box 130)
  - Energy Crisis (Folder 1797, Box 130)
  - English Electric Power Lines (Folder 1798, Box 130)
  - Environmental Concerns (Folder 1799, Box 130)
  - Environmental Defense Fund (Folder 1800, Box 130)
  - Environmental Education - Taormina Lectures (Folder 1801, Box 130)
  - Environmental Planning Lobby (Folder 1802, Box 130)
  - Environmental Programs, Symposia, Meeting Plans (Folder 1803, Box 130)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (Folder 1804, Box 130)
  - Everglades (Folder 1805, Box 130)
  - Federal Communication Commission (FCC) (Folder 1806, Box 131)
  - Films (Folder 1807, Box 131)
  - Fire Island National Seashore (Folder 1808, Box 131)
  - Fish of the Hudson, John S. Grim (Folder 1809, Box 131)
  - Forest Preserve (Folder 1810, Box 131)
  - Gas (Folder 1811, Box 131)
  - Gas - Clippings (Folder 1812, Box 131)
  - Gas Turbines (Folder 1813, Box 131)
  - Gas Turbines (Folder 1814, Box 131)